Guide to the Development and Alumni Affairs, School of Nursing, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Development and Alumni Affairs, School of Nursing, Yale University, records
1976-2003
RU 1029
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3
(3 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, meeting minutes, and reports of the Development and Alumni Affairs office documenting services and support for Yale School of Nursing alumni.
Yale University. School of Nursing
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 29-E (YRG 29-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Nursing.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from Development and Alumni Affairs, Yale School of Nursing, 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic, thereunder chronologically.
Biographical / Historical
The Yale School of Nursing Development and Alumni Affairs office is responsible for alumni relations and fundraising, and serves as liaison to the Alumnae/i Association.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, meeting minutes, and reports of the Development and Alumni Affairs office documenting services and support for Yale School of Nursing alumni.
Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University. School of Nursing; Yale University. School of Nursing. Alumnae/i Association
- Development and alumni affairs records, 1973-2003; Accession 2007-A-145
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2038
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged by topic.
  - Reunion, 1996-2002
    - Reunion Weekend, Misc, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1947 Book, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Reunion Weekend, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Program, Speakers, CVs, Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Distinquished alumni, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Monograph, 75th anniversary, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Program, Speakers, CVs, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting: Agenda, Slate of Officers, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Distinguished Alum, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Evaluations, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Housing (Hotels/Dorm), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Phone List/check list/misc., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Annual meeting & Slate, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Distinguished Alumns, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Reservations, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Programs, Speakers, CVs, Correspondence, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Registration Packet: Chair Order/Maps, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Mailings, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Evaluations, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Programs, Speakers, CVs, Correspondence, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Housing, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Evaluations, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Reservations, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Phone List/check list/misc., 2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Distinguished Alum, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Magnets, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Programs, Speakers, CVs, Correspondence, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Annual Meeting, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Distinguished Alum, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Evaluations, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Black Book, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - "Launching Your Career" Workshop
    - 1995 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 2000 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 2002 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - YSN Alumnae/i Association
    - Constitution & Bylaws, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Boards, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 43 - 44)
    - Alum Weekend, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Board, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - AYA, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Board Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Bookkeeping, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Board Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 50 - 51)
    - Bookkeeping, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Board Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Bookkeeping, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - CEU Application, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Board Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Bookkeeping, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Alumnae Events, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - AYA, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Alumni Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Board Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Bookkeeping, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Alumni Fund, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - AYA, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Board Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Bookkeeping, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Reunions, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Class of 1942 Reunion Misc., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - "Back Talk", 1997 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - AYA, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Alumni Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Alumni Records, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Bookkeeping, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Board Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Reunions, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Alumni Fund, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Board Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Alumni Records, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - AYA, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - 75th Anniversary, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Video, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Class Photo Project, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Board Meetings, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Alumni Fund, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Alumni Records, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - AYA, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Reunions, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Alumni Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Board Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Board Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Reunions, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Board Meetings, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - AYA, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Alumni Fund, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Board Meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Alumnae/i Association Logos, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Slate of Officers, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Constitution / Bylaws, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - AYA Meeting, 2002 February (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Reunions, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Diers Retirement, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Class Agents, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Distinguished Alum, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - DAA Bowls, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Distinguished Alum Award, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - General Info DAA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - DAA Recipients, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Service to the School Award, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Nomination Forms, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Nomination Worksheets, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Criteria for Selection, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - DAA's, 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - DAA Awards, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - DAA, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 125 - 127)
    - DAA: Nominees, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - YSN Alumnae Awards, 1973-1982 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - DAA Citations, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Pin Ceremony Information, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Needlepoint Patterns, undated (Box 3, Folder 132)